{
    "id": "9d1744963b1b41dbba15d5d57cf98950",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. watch a lot of movies when I was younger.",
            "description": "Either would or used to can be used to talk about past habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ecd3001949a749ada1181afb4799fa7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………. in the morning.",
            "description": "To simply say that something happened some time ago, we use the simple past.",
            "answers": [
                "have arrived",
                "arrived",
                "had arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0513ec1c8ac4449ac070f091d9aedd9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ..................................... unhappy since her divorce.",
            "description": "To talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present, we use the present perfect tense.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "090ba8c47d0f4e1ebb9a39563475a766"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ my uncle when I was in Canada.",
            "description": "To simply say that something happened some time ago, we use the simple past.",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "have visited",
                "had visited"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0882131906144306bf348f44b217b0a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… him instantly.",
            "description": "To simply say that something happened some time ago, we use the simple past.",
            "answers": [
                "was recognizing",
                "recognized",
                "have recognized"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb69391465b4412e839f4e4f6782cde7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody ………………………………. the cat in.",
            "description": "When there is no time reference, we use the present perfect to talk about finished events.",
            "answers": [
                "let",
                "has let",
                "was let"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d28851224b5c4b0b93c15cad0a85737c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who …………………………….. the door open?",
            "description": "When the emphasis is on the person who committed the action, the simple past is used. ",
            "answers": [
                "has left",
                "left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9bea66f0bf1f4ace8e42d2e5876b6d25"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. in this town since I was a child.",
            "description": "The present perfect or the present perfect continuous is used to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "lived",
                "have lived",
                "had lived"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "935d9653f2bd431da5cbe933fcfb446c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… hiking yesterday.",
            "description": "To simply say that something happened some time ago, we use the simple past.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fdf7a07c71bb4538bc23298d684b3072"
        },
        {
            "question": "No one …………………………………. him since that fateful day.",
            "description": "We use the present perfect to talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "has seen",
                "saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc327973208d4367b0355e6f2de245d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The birds …………………………….. and sold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have caught",
                "were caught",
                "had caught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02e0573f36824419bdbd964b8454a60b"
        },
        {
            "question": "As soon as she finished one project, she ………………………………. working on the next.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was started",
                "has started",
                "started"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd7fe113e88f49a4800132698ebbd9d7"
        }
    ]
}